// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What was Rizal's first poem?",
    answer: "Sa aking mga kababata",
    options: [
      "Mi último adiós",
      "Sa aking mga kababata",
      "Himno al Trabajo",
      "A la juventud filipina"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the title of Rizal's unfinished novel in Tagalog?",
    answer: "Nakamisa",
    options: [
      "Laban Bayan",
      "Lapastangan",
      "Nakamisa",
      "Huwaran"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the oldest sister of Rizal?",
    answer: "Saturnina",
    options: [
      "Paciano Rizal",
      "Narcisa Mercado",
      "Saturnina",
      "Josefa Mercado"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When and where did Rizal start formal schooling?",
    answer: "Biñan on 1869",
    options: [
      "Biñan on 1869",
      "Ateneo de Manila on 1872",
      "University of Santo Tomas on 1877",
      "City College of Calamba on 1878"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What was Rizal’s first winning literary piece on the competition sponsored by the Artistic-Literary Lyceum?",
    answer: "A la juventud filipina",
    options: [
      "Mi último adiós",
      "Sa aking mga kababata",
      "Himno al Trabajo",
      "A la juventud filipina"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the complete legal name of Dr. Jose Rizal?",
    answer: "José Protacio Rizal Mercado y Alonso Realonda",
    options: [
      "José Protacio Rizal Mercado y Alonso Realonda",
      "Dr. Josito Alonso Realonda Mercado Rizal",
      "Dr. Jose Protacio Alonso Realondo Martinez Rizal",
      "Dr. Jose Pedro Alonso Realonda Mercado Rizal"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What was the date of birth of Dr. Jose Rizal?",
    answer: "June 19, 1861",
    options: [
      "June 19, 1861",
      "May 19, 1761",
      "July 19, 1871",
      "June 18, 1961"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the Spanish name for a Filipino native, which the Filipinos resented?",
    answer: "Indio",
    options: [
      "Indio",
      "Hudio",
      "Pinoy",
      "Alferez"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Name Rizal's host at Wilhelmsfeld.",
    answer: "Karl Ulmer",
    options: [
     "Karl Ulmer",
     "Dr. Reinhold Rost",
      "Dr. Ferdinand Blumettritt",
     "Dr. Jagor"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "At 16, Rizal experienced his first romance. He fell in love with which girl?",
    answer: "Segunda Katigbak",
    options: [
     "Leonor Gonzalez",
     "Leonor Rivera",
      "Segunda Katigbak",
     "Getrude Beckett"
    ]
   },
];